5.5.5
Fixed the problem that when the minimum value of the scroll bar control is set to a negative number, the negative value becomes the maximum value when scrolling.
Fix the window centering function of the control. The selected control is centered separately, and the selected control should be centered in the entire group.
Fixed the problem that Hscroll control cannot be compiled when the main window is in Chinese.
Fix the problem that the focus frame is not displayed in the window editing when the code and window editing are split.
Added side and bottom, in the code editing state, you can choose to hide in the view menu, or click the code text of the code design button to switch the display.
Added a new mouse wizard template, you can use this to copy the script recorded by [Yongfang Mouse Wizard] to directly generate the software.
Added a ruler display in the edit area of ​​the window
Added start group homepage, which is convenient for operation, and the homepage cannot be closed.
Optimization Switch to window editing to display the window faster.
Optimization Code function positioning (the current function name is displayed at the top when the code is edited) is changed to delay in real time. Keep dragging the selection code up and down without changing the card.
Optimization When pasting a control, if it encounters an array control with the same name, it is directly judged as a control array and no longer asks whether to create a control array.
Optimization Opening the same project after opening multiple VFBs will be prevented from opening.

5.5.4
Fixed the problem that the mouse out event of the BUTTON control is invalid during self-drawing.
Fixed the problem of misalignment of controls in the window alignment function without compensation under high DPI.
Fixed the problem that the timer control would be invalid after opening the same window.
Fixed an error in obtaining the first letter of pinyin, which caused the code prompt to be unable to search for the Chinese code with the first letter.
Adjust the Miniblink control DLL update to the latest version 2021-3-24, change the DLL name to mb.dll and mb64.dll

5.5.3 2021-2-24
Fixed the problem that the project and window list labels disappear when the VFB is closed and the VFB is opened next time after using the plug-in.
Fixed the problem of wrong English letters in the TVN_SetDispInfo event name of the TreeView control.
Fix the problem of invalid click in the help of project properties and image management.
Fix the problem that there is no space before the variable member AS in the help making.

New project and window labels are added, "X" is displayed on the right of the current selection, click to close.
Add a drop-down button at the end of the window label, click as the menu, and select the file in the current project.
Added synchronization in VFB help, click on the list to automatically open related entries.

When the remaining project is changed, the project label is also displayed.
Change Close other tabs, only close other tabs of the current project, other projects will not be closed.
Change the automatic backup by typing 100 characters, and adjust it to backup after 60 seconds after typing 1 character.

5.5.2 2021-2-12 New Year's Day
Fixed an issue where ListView.GetItemText would crash if it exceeded 260 characters. Adjusted to a maximum of 2048 characters, it won’t crash even if it exceeds 260 characters.
Fixed the problem that class functions, procedures, attributes, etc. were not in the function list of the code editor.
Fix the problem that the entry modification date is 1970-1-1 after syncing the help.
Fix the problem that the referenced file cannot be opened in "Go to the defined position" in the right-click menu of the code.
Fix to avoid short keyword hints not coming out, such as App
Fixed the problem that when searching on the library page, 3 items are always found for 1 keyword.
Fix the problem that the code prompt will not prompt correctly after using the keywords in the extended library or the source code library as the variable name.
Fix the problem of lack of static library when using network_UDP_Create (libiocp_socket.a file is put into the compiler folder)

Added a help prompt area, prompting function parameters, related other keywords, and quoting files
Newly added There are multiple keyword categories in the help prompt area, only the last one is displayed, the others are collapsed, click the small triangle to expand and display all.
Add "Go to definition position" in the right-click menu of the code, which belongs to the entry in the help, and the help will be opened directly to locate this entry.

Change Miniblink control with the latest version 20210131 32-bit and 64-bit DLL
Change the variable name of the current process or function in the help prompt area
Change the entry in the library list, and the complete information can also be prompted in the help area.
When changing the search and replace, avoid the automatic replacement of upper and lower case and cause lagging imagination.
Change When a keyword is encountered and multiple entries are found, the help prompt content will no longer be prompted together.

5.5.1 2021-1-21
Added a help prompt area, click a keyword to open related help.
Added automatic replacement of keyword case
The newly added entries belong to different categories, and all code hints will be displayed.
Added the theme properties of the TreeView and ListView controls to make the style the same as the theme of the WIN system resource manager.
Added Chinese code can be prompted by typing the first letter of pinyin (only for the document edited by the current project, not public library and private library)

Fix the right-click menu of the library file in the project, it will crash when opening the folder
Fixed the problem of slow loading templates when opening the new project in the project window and clicking the VFB and BAS projects next to it.
Fix the problem of continuously declaring variables in the current function, and the first variable is not recognized by the code prompt.
Amendment Avoid automatic replacement and insertion of code for non-code files. Judging by the extension. Code file: "INC""BI""FRM""BAS"
Amendment The synchronization window modification button in the help is not initially disabled, and cannot be changed with the tick in the list
The parameter prompt of class member is incorrect.
Fix the problem that the help file is not displayed in the recycle bin after deleting a member.

Change and adjust the code hint sorting strategy. Procedures and functions are ranked first, and constants are ranked behind.
Change Miniblink control with the latest version 20210114 32-bit and 64-bit DLL
Change the public library to make a lot of changes

5.5.0 2021-1-11
New window event: WM_KeyDown WM_KeyUp
New SQLite3 control adds UpdateText function for writing large amounts of text or special text.
Added SQLite3 control query, modification, update and other parameters to UTF8 character functions to avoid many internal conversions when directly using UTF8 characters.
Add Miniblink control to call JS function and some other functions, add parameter to UTF8 character function.
Added a new help system integrated with help and code hints and a re-created database. Support cloud function, everyone can participate in repairing the library, and can update simultaneously.
New Add index, search, and collection in the library prompt, which is to integrate the help system in the built-in VFB (implemented by plug-in)
Newly added TreeView control new item adds sub-property parameters, some event descriptions, ExpandEx function, fixes the problem of image index modification.
Added an icon is added to the project list, and the icon file is in vfb\Settings\img, which can be modified arbitrarily.
New ImageList control added to load images from files

Fixed the problem that the name of the entire Chinese module or window file may cause the same name of the temporary compiled file.
Fixed the UTF8 output property of CWSTR. When there are many characters, random crash codes will occur.
Amendment After changing the name of the window, when switching to design mode from other places, sometimes the prompt window name duplication problem occurs.
Fixed the problem that there is no keyboard message in the main window.
Fixed some errors in binding other controls. For example, the list control is bound to the image list control, causing the binding to fail during compilation.
Fix In the window template, the window creation event should not be at the top of the code area after the control is created, but should be behind it.
Fix the problem that the text input box does not automatically follow the window to adjust the size after the text modification window is resized in the control properties.
Fixed the problem that the font setting in yGDI did not follow the self-defined DPI scaling and only responded to the system DPI.
Fixed the problem that the code prompt did not change the position when moving the window and scrolling the code editing.
Fixed the problem of inconsistent font size in the parameter prompt of the code prompt when the DPI is high. And increase the display of the parameters in the prompt. There is also a hint that the calculation of the width and height of the window is a bit inaccurate.
Fixed the problem that the GetDIR function would return the ".." folder when the folder is empty.
Fix the problem that all events are invalid for all virtual controls when the window name is Chinese.
Fix the feeling of stuck when dragging the selection code with the mouse.
When opening a new file, the current function name is not prompted in the Combo control in the code editor

When changing and pasting the control, it is set according to the position of the pop-up menu of the right mouse button.
Change all the controls, you can select and drag arbitrarily outside the main window
When changing the design window, you can drag the scroll bar to a certain distance from the left and the top.
Change the control to show a pure line style outside of its main window.
Change the Miniblink1 control header definition file.
Change When the height of the code prompt window exceeds the main VFB window, the code prompt window will be displayed above the cursor.
Change the space in front of the comment quotation mark. In the past, any number was allowed not to be processed for manual alignment, but it was changed to one for automatic code alignment.
Changing the code formatting will no longer smooth out the format of the comment line. When commenting, set the single quote position according to the format position of all lines being annotated, instead of adding a single quotation mark to the first character that was crude before.
The opened project list is saved only when the original VFB is closed, and it is used to automatically open the VFB next time. It is changed to automatically save the list every time a project is opened, so that the computer crashes or the software crashes, etc., the VFB can be restored to the upper when the VFB is reopened. The sub-project status is now.
After opening the file, replace chr(9) with a space to avoid errors in code analysis and judgment.
Change the toolbar icon, partly replaced with ICO file In vfb\Settings\img\tool
Changes Enhanced help prompts, code prompts, kernel code improvements, etc.

5.4.10 2020-11-11
Fix the problem of abnormal opening of the project
Fix the problem that when the class member is a pointer, the pointer member is not prompted.
Fix the problem of \\ path in new project
Fixed the issue that the BackColor ForeColor of the ListView control does not take effect.
Fixed the problem that Miniblink control, 32-bit software, did not automatically respond to system DPI.
Fix the code analysis system, when it encounters a character string and a long line character, the problem of judging whether it is a long line or not.
Correct the warning prompt in MEM_Read_Dword.
Fixed the problem that characters can be input in the version number in the project properties.
Fix the problem that the internal data record is not updated when the code changes the position and size of the real control.
Fixed the problem that may crash when opening the project in WIN10 system.

Change the Utf8toStr function, there is a BUG report that the memory application failed, and use a byte array instead.
Change the TreeView control Expand from function to property
Change the control related data changed from API GetProp to self-written function processing (the speed is improved and the platform will not worry about it in the future) The control interface is also upgraded, and the self-written control needs to be rewritten and compiled.
Change Only the compilation number of the file version number will be +1 if the compilation is successful (no compilation error)
Change the code to modify the position and size of the virtual control, and change it to the actual value of the real control (previously DPI 100% value) to avoid confusion (it will mess up the set when it is not 100% DPI)
Change Download the VFB compressed package without a compiler. When compiling, if there is no compiler, it will be downloaded and installed automatically.
Change Click the assembly debugging software in the tool menu, it will automatically download and install this software.

Added support for code formatting and display dividing lines of Operator statements
Added ListView control added TextBkColor property
Added IsExecutableAddress function to determine whether the memory address is valid.

5.4.9 2020-11-1
Fix the problem of a crash when the file does not exist when adding a new window, adding a file, etc.
In the control list, except for all lists, other scroll bars are abnormal.
Fixed the problem that after copying and pasting the control, the copied control property content was not copied.

Improvement When dragging the scroll bar in the control list, the mouse can be dragged away from the scroll bar when dragging.
Improve CWstr to support Boolean type

5.4.8 2020-10-31
Improved more sensitive and efficient bracket matching prompt
Improved After selection, the function of selecting the same character is highlighted, which is more sensitive and efficient.
Improve code hints to remove abstract, virtual, CONST and operator when extracting type content
Improvement The window is too small when opening VFB for the first time, it is automatically judged to be a suitable size

Change The plug-in menu is independent from the tools menu, because the number of plug-ins will become more and more important.
Change the control display area of ​​the window editing, except that all the controls are displayed with a single icon, the others are displayed in the form of a list, which is convenient to find the controls.
Change the folder when the project is saved, and the default folder is changed to the project output folder.
Change the class for saving control data and increase the value of CtlData(99) to save data when writing controls. (Controls written by yourself need to be recompiled, otherwise they will crash)
Change the track record of the code editor. When the position change is less than 20 lines, the track will no longer be recorded.

Added optional, show space symbol
New optional, display the background color of the first line of a function or procedure (including type and ENUM)
Added optional, display function or process end horizontal line
After the newly added code editor is double-divided, both code editors will be highlighted after selecting the content.
Added common code editing options in the View menu
New code formatting function Added smart code alignment function.
Newly added a bound image list control in the edit properties of the mCtrlTreeList control
When adding an automatic function definition, EXTERN and END EXTERN are automatically added.
Newly add new project plug-in, increase project folder setting, you can freely specify folder.
Added Open the controls and plug-ins in the project and add a remark column, so that everyone can understand what it is.

Fixed the problem that the font cannot be displayed correctly when the code editor option is first opened.
Fix the problem of grabbing the current focus after auto-saving.
Fix the problem that the focus is still on the code editor when the tab is in the window state, causing the keyboard operation to modify the code.
Fixed the problem that the code formatting did not format the continuous variables behind DIM AS